So friends, ICICI Lombard General
Insurance Company has disclosed its Quarter 3
numbers. So let's see
what is there in the Quarter 3 numbers.
This data is basically given at the end.
I will convert it to a course for you to
understand. It will be easier to understand.
If we look at the total income of the company in the last quarter, then
in the last quarter the company
generated revenue of around ₹4499 crores through total income.
Talking about last year, last
year it was
around ₹3854 crores, which if seen at this quantum of increase, is
around ₹4362 crores. So you can say
that the company's growth this year has been almost
upset by around 12%,
but when we go quarter to quarter,
you are seeing a decline of approximately 2% there. So overall,
this means that the
company is flat quarter to quarter, but if we look at the year to year,
you are probably seeing a strong increase of 12%.
Let's look at the company's expenses.
What has the company spent?
In the last quarter, the company  It spent 3988 crores and
last year it spent 3521 crores whereas the
company's expenses in this water are around 485 crores.
So what did I tell you that the
company's revenue has
fallen by 2% compared to the last quarter, but when it comes to the company's expenses, the
company has not controlled it. The
company's expenses are higher than the last quarter, due to which the
company's
profit has seen a decline compared to the previous quarter. So let's
look at the company's profit, what should we make, if we
look at the company in the last cut, it would have been
₹590 crores, last year it would have been ₹370 crores.
What did I tell you that the company
's profit has fallen in this area, so in this quadrant the
company's profit has fallen to around 352 crores. So if you
look at the year from last year, then the last
two years are very good because as
I told you Sardar Sir, the company's
revenue is also 12% bigger, if we
look at the profit of the company, then the profit of the company has also
seen an increase of approximately 15%, but when we take into account the deductions  So, the
revenue of Kota company is surrounded by 2%
and if we go into the profit of the company, then the
profit of the company can almost be said that
you are seeing a decline of around 40%,
so the company's revenue is good, the
property of the company is also good, but
if the company had controlled its expenses a little
in this quarter, then the
numbers could have been good and
a slight rise could have been seen in the share,
but just because the company did not control
its expenses in this quarter, due to which the
profit of the company is seen decreasing in this quarter compared to the previous quarter,
let's look at the earnings, if we look at the
earnings, last year it used to be
around 6.47,
now it is 7.18, but in the last quarter the
company's earnings were around Rs 12, so
clearly you must have seen that the numbers of the company
are a bit weak, but the year 10
year numbers are very strong, so let's
see how the market edits it,
but according to me, nothing much is going to happen.  I
need two-four questions above or two-four
persons below, that's all that will happen, nothing more than this, so that's all
for today, if you
like the video then please like it and also
subscribe to the channel,
thank you.